export const avengers = [
  {
    question:
      "During which war did Captain America get his superhuman abilities?",
    options: ["Civil War", "World War I", "World War II", "The Cold War"],
    answer: "World War II",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following characters did not disappear during the ”blip”?",
    options: ["Spiderman", "Black Panther", "Doctor Strange", "Iron Man"],
    answer: "Iron Man",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Thor's mother's name?",
    options: ["Frya", "Feera", "Fridda", "Frigga"],
    answer: "Frigga",
  },
];

export const sports = [
  {
    question: "Term Chinaman is related to which sports ?",
    options: ["Football", "Hockey", "Cricket", "Golf"],
    answer: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question: "With which game does Davis Cup is associated",
    options: ["Hockey", "Polo", "Lawn Tennis", "Cricket"],
    answer: "Lawn Tennis",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of person which controls a football match",
    options: ["A Referee", "A Spectator", "An Umpire", "A Goalkeeper"],
    answer: "A Referee",
  },
];

export const travel = [
  {
    question: "Which river of India is called Vridha Ganga?",
    options: ["Krishna", "Godavari", "Kaveri", "Narmada"],
    answer: "Godavari",
  },
  {
    question: "Which foreign country is closest to Andaman Islands",
    options: ["Sri Lanka", "Indonesia", "Pakitan", "Nepal"],
    answer: "Sri Lanka",
  },
  {
    question: "The state having largest area under waste land is",
    options: ["Rajastan", "Gujarat", "Madhya Pradesh", "Jammu and kashmir"],
    answer: "Rajastan",
  },
];

export const technology = [
  {
    question: "'OS' computer abbreviation usually means ?",
    options: [
      "Order of Significance",
      "Open Software",
      "Operating System",
      "Optical Sensor",
    ],
    answer: "Operating System",
  },
  {
    question: "'.MOV' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    options: [
      "Image file",
      "Animation/movie file",
      "Audio file",
      "MS Office document",
    ],
    answer: "Animation/movie file",
  },
  {
    question: "'DB' computer abbreviation usually means ?",
    options: ["Database", "Double Byte", "Data Block", "Driver Boot"],
    answer: "Database",
  },
];

export const science = [
  {
    question: "The working principle of a washing machine is",
    options: ["Reverse osmosis", "Diffusion", "Centrifugation", "Dialysis"],
    answer: "Centrifugation",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is used in pencils?",
    options: ["Graphite", "Silicon", "Charcoal", "Phosphorous"],
    answer: "Graphite",
  },
  {
    question: "Chemical formula for water is",
    options: ["NaAlO2", "H2O", "Al2O3", "CaSiO3"],
    answer: "H2O",
  },
];

export const language = [
  {
    question:
      "Correct the sentence gramatically: She went to gym despite of her illness.",
    options: ["to", "of", "despite", "none of the above"],
    answer: "of",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Choose the correct verb form from those in brackets. The earth _ round the sun.",
    options: ["moves", "moved", "move", "none of the above"],
    answer: "moves",
  },
  {
    question: "Correction of sentences: What your Sirname is?",
    options: [
      "What your Sirname?",
      "What is your Sirname?",
      "Your Sirname is what?",
      "none of the above",
    ],
    answer: "What is your Sirname?",
  },
];

export const animals = [
  {
    question: "What animal has the worst shortest memory?",
    options: ["Dog", "Elephant", "Rat", "Dolphin"],
    answer: "Elephant",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following has no Skeleton at all?",
    options: ["Star fish", "Sponge", "Silver fish", "Jelly fish"],
    answer: "Jelly fish",
  },
  {
    question: "Which living bird lays the world's largest egg?",
    options: ["Eagle", "Owl", "Ostrich", "Vulture"],
    answer: "Ostrich",
  },
];

export const categories = [
  {
    name: "Movies",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1594909122845-11baa439b7bf?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Avengers",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1561149877-84d268ba65b8?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1935&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Sports",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1575361204480-aadea25e6e68?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1471&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Travel",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521295121783-8a321d551ad2?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Technology",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1617791160536-598cf32026fb?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1064&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Science",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1532094349884-543bc11b234d?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1470&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Language",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1634128221889-82ed6efebfc3?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80",
  },
  {
    name: "Animals",
    img: "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521651201144-634f700b36ef?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1170&q=80",
  },
];
